footballpredictions.net 2019-06-24

# Privacy

**European Union Visitors**  
Visitors from the European Union are protected by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) legislation. 

At FootballPredictions.NET we have put in place a number of changes to make sure that, as a European Union located visitor, you are provided with adequate privacy settings as required by the GDPR.

  * We do not collect and store any personal information anywhere on our website through entry forms, registration forms, or any other form of data entry. 
  * We have updated our Google Analytics settings to ensure that your IP address will not be stored by Google in a format that will make you personally identifiable (click here for more technical information about Google Analytics Anonymization) 
  * We now provide you with the ability to add and remove your consent for us to use cookies (see below to update your consent). 

**What We Collect**  
We may collect the following information when you use our website:

  * Demographic information, namely the country from which you are viewing our website
  * Statistical information about the pages you are viewing, by use of Google Analytics
  * Preferences and settings - for example your odds style preference, mobile or desktop preference, and your consent (or not) for us to use cookies. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How FootballPredictions.NET Uses Cookies**  
We use cookies to personalise content and advertisements to make our website relevant to you, and to analyse our traffic. We also use cookies to ensure that our website is legally compliant with laws and regulations in different countries and regions of the world. For example, we may be restricted from showing you links to certain sportsbooks where these companies do not have a licence to operate in your country.

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a small text file which is placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit websites.

Almost all websites use cookies. Cookies are used to help analyse web traffic, store your preferences, and track the path of your visit to a website from page to page to assist in caching and performance when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow websites to respond to you as an individual. The web site can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by remembering information about your preferences.

FootballPredictions.NET uses cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us to improve our website in order to tailor it to your needs. We use this information for statistical analysis purposes, in particular Google Analytics.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to see which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any specific and personal information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

**Your Agreement To Allow FootballPredictions.NET To Set Cookies**  
We are required by relevant laws and directives to inform you that FootballPredictions.NET uses cookies and we are required to gain your consent to allow us to place cookies on your device. This is why we have explicitly placed a message about the use of cookies on our website pages to direct you to this page to make you fully aware of how our website operates.

The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of our website. For all other types of cookies we need your permission.

This site may use different types of cookies now, or in the future as defined by this policy. Some cookies may also be placed by third party services that appear on our pages.

Your consent applies to the following domain only: www.FootballPredictions.NET  

**What To Do If You Do Not Want Cookies**  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies through your browser, or for our website only. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you would like to learn more about how to manage the acceptance of cookies on your own browser or device, please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx

**Types Of Cookie**  
While using FootballPredictions.NET you may have one or two different types of cookie set on your device. These are 1st Party and 3rd Party Cookies and are now explained.

**1st Party Cookies**  
1st party cookies are cookies that are set and used by FootballPredictions.NET.  
The cookies listed below are necessary cookies (unless otherwise specified) that help make our website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation, content display, our own legal obligations to show or not show you content, and your preferences. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.

Below you will find a full list of the 1st party necessary cookies that FootballPredictions.NET uses:

Cookie Name | Purpose  
---|---  
odds | This is a cookie that stores your odds style preference - fractional or decimal. This enables us to show odds on our website in your preferred format. By default this cookie is not set. It is only set if you explicitly choose a different setting on our settings page.   
tz | This cookie stores your preference of timezone, enabling us to tailor the event times of, for example, football matches to your specification. By default it is set to at our system’s best guess of your current timezone and may be changed by you using our menus.   
country | This is a cookie that stores the country in the world that you are browsing our website from.e.g. United Kingdom. This cookie helps us tailor our content to users from that country, for example to ensure that we only display content to you that is legally allowed in your country.   
laravel_session | This cookie is integral to the programming language that our website is coded in. These cookies help our web server establish that you are the same user when you browse from page to page (i.e. they help our web server identify your 'session'. Session cookies are almost always deleted when you exit your browser and are only meant to help our web server identify your session while you browse our website, and help you by performing actions such as caching pages that you might visit multiple times within the same session.   
XSRF-TOKEN | This cookie is used for security protection to prevent XSS attacks.  
  
**3rd Party Cookies**  
These cookies are set by other companies and organisations that FootballPredictions.NET works with, or uses software they provide.  
FootballPredictions.NET partners with a number of organisations and other websites to provide you content. For example, we display the latest free bet offers from a number of external companies.  
The cookies that these companies may set while you use FootballPredictions.NET are termed 3rd Party Cookies because they are not directly set by FootballPredictions.NET, but are instead set by the external company. 

Below you will find a list of the 3rd Party organisations that FootballPredictions.NET works with.

Cookie(s) | Organisation | Cookie and Privacy Policy  
---|---|---  
_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmt  
_utmz  
_gat  
_ga  
_gid  |  Google  | 

These cookies are used for Google Analytics. FootballPredictions.NET tracks visitor statistics through the use of Google Analytics, as do most websites, and these cookies are required to enable us to count the number of visitors to our website and analyse general and global statistics about our visitors. Doing this helps us improve FootballPredictions.NET and tailor our content to provide you the best user experience. We have taken steps to configure our Google Analytics so that Google will not store any data about you that can personally identify you. For example, we anonymise your IP address in Google Analytics, and we do not define any URLs on our website that contain data that is personal to you, and therefore will not be stored by Google.

**Links To Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have clicked these links to leave our site, please note that we do not have any control over these external websites.

Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

If, at any time in the future we collect personal information (with your consent), we will not sell, distribute or lease personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
By law, you may request details of personal information which we hold about you. At present we do not hold any information that personally identifies any individual.

If you would like to contact us, please use our contact form. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
